onefile.net 2008-05-05

# Untitled Page

**Privacy** Policy

OneFile™ has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. As part of the normal operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**1\. Information Collected During Your Use of the OneFile™ Service.**   
In order to register, users are required to give us contact information (e.g., your name and email address), unique identifiers (e.g., your password), and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity and for use in our records. 

During your usage of OneFile™ we will need to collect certain financial information, such as your W2's, bank statements, and other legal documents. Financial Information that is collected is used to check your qualifications for registration, to bill you for products and services, and for other purposes. OneFile™ does not share Financial Information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with it's Solutions. 

**2\. Our Use of Your Information**   
We use the information and documents provided solely for the purpose of your membership. At no time is your information used for other activity. 

**3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**   
We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy and without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

OneFile™ will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any of you or your business' personally identifiable information to any third party. 

**4\. Security**   
In order to maximize the protection of your information, OneFile™' Service uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your legal documents, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet. 

**5\. General**   
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the OneFile™ Agreement. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please contact us.
